Hey, Levia...
Aren't you a bit too relaxed?!
Huh? You think so?
All right, ready to go?
Oh, very well.
I'll tag along with you, no matter how far!
You said that with such a
cool look just yesterday!
What's the problem?
It's not like there's anything to do until
we get to the Beastmen continent.
Yeah, true, but still...
Besides, I'm on boat duty
after we get to the port.
Seems like a small price to pay to
employ a god of the seas for free.
Well, I mean...
The war stopped all ships,
so there's no other way.
Can't you do some magic that lets us
jump all the way there in one go?
Transfer magic?
Yeah, do that. You're a sea god, right?
What do you think a god of the seas is?
Transfer magic is a huge hassle.
Years of preparation!
Extreme magic power!
It's not something you can just throw around.
I guess nobody would use horse-drawn
carriages or ships if it were that easy.
Travel takes effort. So...
It only makes sense to receive proper
compensation for that, don't you think?
We stopped.
Thank you!
Sorry!
We'd like to share this ride with
you until we get to town...
Big Sis?
What, you know her?
Long time no see, Crybaby Alizee!
Master Setsu...
That was a long time ago!
I'm not a crybaby anymore!
I'm not going to cry!
Episodul 6
Maestru și ucenic pentru a doua oară
This is Alizee Ifreel.
We traveled together for a while
the last time I was summoned.
I am Master Setsu's top pupil!
I don't remember ever
taking you on as a pupil.
What are you talking about?!
You taught me the fundamentals of combat
every night, physically and painstakingly!
Every night, physically, huh?
Okay, I get that he's my sister's teacher.
And who are you?
Oh, this is Amelle.
I'm Alizee's little sister!
You have a sister?
Well, more like... things kind
of ended up that way.
I'm her sister! We lived together!
Only for a short while, though.
Like master, like pupil, huh?
Anyway, Master, where have you been for five
whole years? Leaving your top pupil behind?!
Well, about that—
I-I'll explain.
I see.
And now you're trying to thwart Toma's plan.
Traveling across worlds twice,
changing your appearance...
From anyone but you, I'd never believe it.
Yeah, but it's Setsu.
I wasn't expecting any of it, either.
Hey, I know! Alizee, come with
us to the Beastmen continent.
Help me out on my trip,
like you did five years ago.
Certainly!
...would once have been my response, but...
I'm actually caught up in a
serious situation, as well.
I'm sorry. It's all because of me.
Ever since you vanished,
I started taking on jobs fighting monsters
as a continuation of my training.
One day, I accepted a village's
request to slay a dragon.
That village was called Zathrow.
It was a nice, quiet village.
Please use this house while you're with us.
She's an important guest,
so please take care of her.
Hello, I'm Amelle. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Do you like it?
Yes. Back at Evilbarrow, it's hard
to find food this fresh right now.
Right, you're at war with the humans...
Oh, I have fruits, too!
You don't have to go to so much trouble.
Do you live here all alone?
No, this...
used to be my brother's house.
Your brother?
I'm not from this village.
My brother found me about two years ago.
He said, "Starting today, we're a family."
So I lived here with him, but...
He hasn't come home since the
day the dragon first appeared.
So I'm alone again.
But it's fine! I've been alone all
of my life, so I'm used to it.
Amelle, this is a nice village.
The food is good, and the villagers are kind.
I'm growing a bit tired of traveling,
so once this issue is settled,
I'd like to stay here for a while.
Oh, please do! This house is
too big for me to live in alone.
So, during that time,
you can treat me as a sister.
Would you really be my big sister?
Sure. I mean, if it's okay with you.
Of course, Big Sis!
Can I ask you something?
Is Amelle's brother missing because
he was killed by the dragon?
Hey...
Actually, it seems like that's not the case.
Every time there's a dragon attack,
several villagers go missing.
It wasn't just her brother.
Missing?
Yes. Normally, if a dragon attacks,
it leaves some evidence of a battle behind.
Even if the people are defeated,
they should leave something behind.
But everyone disappears without
the slightest trace, no exceptions.
Doesn't sound like a normal attack.
Like they're being spirited away.
I thought the first order of business
would be to defeat the dragon,
so I took a drastic measure.
What are you doing?
I was disabling the ward against evil.
What?! Then the dragon can come right here!
That's the plan.
I'm going to lure it in and beat it here.
But that would put you in danger...
I'll be fine.
It's going to get dangerous here soon,
so head back home, okay?
Okay.
What's wrong?
Well... I wanted to show you this.
How pretty...
Isn't it? I'm good at catching these!
Aw, and I caught that one for you, too...
It kinda tickles when you call me that.
I have to introduce you to Big Bro, too!
Big Sis! Big Sis! Big Sis!
I cornered the dragon and went
after it to finish it off, but...
I lost track of it, so I returned
to the village, only to find...
that the rest of the villagers
had gone missing, as well.
All except for her.
At dawn, I decided to go to the city
to have someone take care of her.
And then you bumped into
us and hitched a ride.
Yes.
If what you said is accurate,
that's a big deal.
An entire village gone missing?
Yes. I want to find her brother and allow
her to live peacefully in the village, but...
I don't understand what's going on.
Do you have any ideas, Master?
Does a "kidnapping dragon" ring any bells?
I've honestly never heard
of anything like that,
but I'm willing to help.
We can't pretend we didn't hear anything.
Really?!
Yeah. My precious pupil
is in trouble, after all.
Master...
Thank you, Master Setsu, and... um...
Mrs. Setsu!
This incident can be explained by...
zombies.
Zombies?
The whole village became the walking dead!
There's actually an evil necromancer
among the villagers.
I don't think there's anyone
like that in my village...
Besides, don't zombies increase
in number, not disappear?
Ah, the rare "Air Zombie."
Once they become zombies,
they become invisible.
Never heard of that before.
So what about the dragon, then?
It was a dragon zombie, of course.
There was a legend in a
country somewhere out east,
about a zombie that became a dragon...
Take this seriously.
Wait, what about a siren, then?
Among sailors, when people go missing,
it's a given that sirens are behind it.
They say a siren's song
draws men into the ocean.
I thought the village was in the mountains.
Who knows?
Maybe there's a siren who lives in the
mountains because they love the food there.
That's just... okay, maybe...
Um, sea monsters have a distinct smell
that makes them easy to identify,
so I don't think that's it.
Oh, Levia-san, you don't smell, of course.
Huh? Do I stink?
I've got it! The culprit is...
Space aliens!
Space aliens?
Everyone knows about them in my world.
They come from the moon aboard
flying saucers and abduct humans.
So they're the—
Setsu, take this seriously.
But, I mean...
What if the dragon that attacked was
an advanced species, like Levia?
It could avoid pursuit by taking
human form and hiding among villagers.
Levia, you could make villagers
vanish without a trace, right?
Stop making me sound bad
just because you're stumped.
I can't and won't do that.
Huh? Levia-san, are you a dragon?
No.
But you do look kind of like one,
don't you think?
Not at all!
Stop comparing me, a god of the seas,
to a mere dragon.
G-God of the seas?
Assuming such a dragon exists,
why didn't it use that magic
to make Alizee disappear?
Excuse me.
It doesn't look like we'll be able to
cross until the water settles down.
Yikes.
What are you going to do
once you reach the city?
I'll go back to the village of Zathrow and
try to find evidence of the lost villagers.
And you were going to do that alone?
Now I have Master.
Big Sis...
Why did the dragon keep attacking
the village over and over, anyway?
Well, maybe it was just really
hungry and saw the humans as prey.
Or maybe it was drawn there by magic power.
Magic power?
The magic power people
use can attract monsters.
For example, if you tried to use
powerful magic inside the village,
some monsters could
potentially be attracted to it.
I see.
One more thing. Why did
the villagers disappear?
Even if magic power was the cause of this,
it doesn't explain that part...
People don't just evaporate into thin air.
They had to have gone somewhere.
Magic powerful enough to attract a dragon...
Doesn't transfer magic fit the description?
You said people vanished after every attack.
What if it was the opposite?
What if the attacks happened
after people vanished?
Do you mean...
There's only one explanation.
They were taken somewhere
using transfer magic.
Every time that happened,
the dragon got lured in by the magic power.
B-But, Master, all magic needs a user.
Are you saying someone was hiding nearby?
Why don't you ask the user themselves?
Think about it.
Transfer magic is no quick task.
It takes years of preparation, right?
But wasn't there a person
who arrived two years ago?
W-Wait... Are you saying you suspect me?
Hold on a minute. That's absurd.
Space aliens were a more
convincing alternative.
Y-Yes, Master!
She's the victim here!
You can't treat her as the bad guy.
At this point, sure.
But I have one more question.
When Levia was telling us the siren story,
do you remember what you said?
N-No...
Sea monsters...
Um, sea monsters have a distinct smell
that makes them easy to identify.
But most demons have a
sense of smell like that.
Levia is out of the ordinary.
Even in her human form,
she doesn't let her magic power leak out.
Of course. I'm a sea god.
Not even Alizee could tell.
So how did you know what Levia really was?
Well, that's because...
I know...
a thing or two about monsters.
What happened?!
She really was a dragon
disguised as a human!
I am Master Setsu's top pupil!
I don't remember ever
taking you on as a pupil.
Do something, top pupil!
Let's go, Alizee!
Right!
Levia!
Got it!
Alizee!
Right!
It's like snow...
Are you sure it was okay
to leave her on her own?
Hmm? Oh, you mean Alizee?
Yeah.
We defeated the dragon,
so she can take it from there alone.
Besides...
Besides?
If she's going to call herself my pupil,
she should finish the jobs she takes on.
Well, how master-like of you.
Amelle...
I should introduce you to them, Big Sis.
To my brother, to the other villagers...
And...
Amelle?! How...
Oh, did you think I was dead?
You really do have a dull sense of smell.
These pets of mine and I have
totally different smells.
Where are the villagers?
They turned into dolls.
They all had strong magic power.
Dolls?
Don't give me that look.
They need magic soldiers for the war.
Amelle, you're...
There was never anyone named Amelle.
Who are you, then?
I am Melluar, the monster master.
Toma-sama gave me that name.
Data viitoare
Vizitând pentru a doua oară
Continentul Semi-Oamenilor
Data viitoare: Visiting the Beastmen
Continent for a Second Time.